GRANT D POWELL

Computer Engineer

931-214-9549 • GrantPowell911@gmail.com • GrantDPowell.github.io • Chattanooga, TN

Summary

As a Computer Engineering major, I've developed strong problem-solving skills, adaptability, and technical knowledge through my academic journey at the University of Tennessee at Chattanooga. My hands-on experience in shift management, cooking, and autobody repair has further honed my ability to tackle diverse challenges. These experiences, combined with my blend of leadership and technical skills, demonstrate my capacity to learn quickly and manage various tasks, preparing me effectively for a career in technology and beyond.

Experience

Walgreens

Shift Manager 08/2021 - Present

- Managed shifts, counted drawers, led truck deliveries, and managed inventory.
- Supported the pharmacy through prescription filling, selling and other tasks.
- Coached and trained team members and walked new members through onboarding process.
- Supervised and led a team of employees, coordinating daily operations and ensuring high levels of customer service and operational efficiency.

Chili's

06/2019 - 01/2021 Kitchen Manager / Cook

- Prepared and cooked food, cleaned, and oversaw shifts as shift leader.
- · Held a strong position and was relied upon in every shift.

Dairy Queen

Line Cook 03/2019 - 06/2019

· Cooked and cleaned.

Mullinax Motors

Autobody Technician 01/2017 - 05/2019

• Auto-repair, auto-body repair, paint prep.

Education

University of Tennessee at Chattanooga

Chattanooga, TN

B.S. in Computer Engineering | GPA: **3.1** / 4.0

08/2020 - 12/2024

- During my time at UTC I have ran numerous study halls / class refresher courses.
- Developed the 'Integrated Lab Companion', an innovative technology for UTC's electrical and computer engineering laboratories, significantly enhancing experimental capabilities and showcasing advanced technical design skills.
- Developed a robust understanding of fundamental computer engineering principles at UTC.
- Graduation Date: December 2024

Skills

Computer Engineering · Python · html5 · Java · C++ · C# · Object Oriented Programming · Linux · Windows · Microcontrollers · Solidworks · Phone repair · PC Building / Repair · Unity

Verbal/Written Communication · Time management · Planning · Organization · Customer service

Achievements



Integrated Lab Companion

Designed the lab companion for UTC electrical engineering laboratories. More Info: https://cpen.vesulo.com/guides/v1.



Tuke TIP 7th grade talent search

I was chosen due to my academic performance to take the ACT early in 7th grade, I achieved a 26.

CERTIFICATIONS